{
    "id": "34f7ae5b7048470bbbd7a1c60218c025",
    "title": "This, That, These and Those",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There is no point in arguing with her. She will never back …………………… .",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Are you sure that she will not back ………………… at the last moment?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "down",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "While writing an essay, you must back ..................................... your arguments with valid examples.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The injured man had to bear .................................. the leather strap while the doctors were stitching up his wounds.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "down",
                "out on",
                "down on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The government should bear ......................................... money launderers and drug traffickers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "down",
                "down on",
                "out on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Though she was under tremendous pressure, she bore ................................... really well.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "in",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The minister was hoping that the scandal would blow .................................... in a couple of weeks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "over",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The terrorists blew the bridge ..................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "out",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "When she found out that he had been cheating on her, she blew ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "down",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The police said that the burglars broke ...................................... shortly after midnight.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "in",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}